thevistaforums.com 2006-05-12

# Windows Vista Forums - Privacy Policy

**1) Visitor Notice.**  
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (Personal Information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you are asked to register before participating on the message boards, entering a contest, or ordering e-mail newsletters. We use your Personal Information for four primary purposes: 

  * To make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.
  * To help you quickly find services or information on Windows Vista Forums.
  * To help us create content most relevant to you.
  * To alert you to special offers, updated information and other new services from Windows Vista Forums.

**2) Visitor Consent.**  
If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of the features on Windows Vista Forums, but you will not be able to access areas that require registration. We may offer newsletters, which are sent only to opt-in lists. They also include a very easy and simple way to be removed once you have joined.

 **3) Security.**  
We strictly protect the security of your personal information and honour your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Your data will be stored on a secure server located at GNAX in Atlanta. The only people who have access to this are the server adminstrators ("A Small Orange Hosting"), and the site admins, William, Aaron, and Anubis. While we try to keep this data safe, there is always the possilibity of security being compromised.

 **4) Distribution of personal information.**  
Windows Vista Forums does not distribute personal information to any third parties. Should this change, we will not distribute any information without your prior express consent. Please be aware that it may be possible, depending on your use of various features on the forums, that some of your personal information is available on publically accessible web page(s). One example would be using the "My Profile" feature in the Invision Power Board software. Consent to expose some of your personal information in these cases is implied by the use of these features.

 **5) Child access.**  
Windows Vista Forums gives children between the ages of 13 and 18 the ability to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. Please take proper measures if you do not wish your child to have access to public forums and message boards. As always, exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in a public forum. If you are younger than 13 years of age, you are forbidden from becoming a member of Windows Vista Forums or posting information on our message boards without direct parental consent.

 **6) Enforcement.**  
If for some reason you believe we have not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail at adminstration@whwh.biz, and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be certain the words "Privacy Policy" are in the Subject line.

 **7) Changes to this document.**  
Changes to this document may be made any time without warning. We may or may not notify you of changes in this policy, however, we will make an effort to notify you if there are any major changes to this policy. You will not be notified about changes related to clarification and/or elaboration of parts of this policy.

 ** _Microsoft, Windows, Vista, Windows Vista, and all related trademarks are either registered trademarks or trademarks of Microsoft Corporation in the United States and/or other countries._**

 ** _Windows Vista Forums is an independent website and is not affiliated with, nor has it been authorized, sponsored, or otherwise approved by Microsoft Corporation._**
